BOOM
Perfection
Yeah!
Sorry it took so long, but I'm there
And there it is! Kurasuno High School's lethal weapon!
The quick attack from first-year duo Shouyo Hinata and Tobio Kageyama
I'm glad that we finally got to see it
And young Hinata stands at a minuscule 164 cm
Making him the shortest hitter out of our two lineups today
Man, that was freakin' fast!
That kid is tiny! Awesome!
Interesting...
That's not the look he had back at the Intensive
Some scary stuff
And then...
Who is this guy?
踢跡が残るくらい拳を固く握り締め
今、wiet星の光の中へ
Woah
夢と感動 暗い生きてく 痛い暗い羽の心臓 鳥肌が止まらない 命が熱く燃えている 喧嘩の先 その先で 戦う喜びは
勝ち負けすらもどこか遠く 時を止めた この一瞬が スローモーションで煌めく さあ暴れな
Kurasado may never be a strong team again. 勝ち負けないままで  concludども たい同じように
少ない 狂 punishingからず付け てもいいかは hip aps 平滅だ として Apr devrait comעθη Madrid
yes nice received little tight see you're such a good
No!
That's true.
Oh, God!
They grow up so fast!
I didn't catch that because of your blubbering.
Don't let number 10 get you distracted.
That spectacular jump practically laughed right in the face of the helpless blockers.
Tsubakihara Academy was completely taken off guard, Joe.
Oh, man, Kageyama, you're a real bastard!
Infuriating!
Biggest jerk ever!
Evil jump!
What the hell is wrong with you guys?
I feel like the gelatin I ate earlier is giving me energy.
Right now, my stomach is in perfect shape.
Back up!
He just served.
He won't have time to get back into the play.
Oh!
Now!
He did it again!
Setter Kageyama glides into position like a hummingbird, Joe!
The young Setter Tobio Kageyama is something of a rising star.
A first-year who was recently invited to train at the All Japan Youth Intensive.
They seem to be arguing about something there, Joe.
I sure hope everything's okay.
Looks like me and my wife.
Damn it!
Man, those new kids are really something.
Yeah.
He's been blessed with so much raw passion.
Sometimes I think that was a problem.
Maybe it's that passion that's kept him in the shadows for so long.
But now...
The whole world is about to discover Tobio Kageyama.
Please, you're exaggerating.
Then again, maybe you're not.
We didn't come here just to stop number 10.
We came here to win the game.
I know I told you to watch him, but that can't be everything.
If we get too focused on him, then we're caught up in their trap.
Widen your view and keep re-blocking.
I guarantee you it will start putting the pressure on them.
Yes, coach!
There's no reason to start panicking.
I won't ask you to do anything you can't do.
Receive the ball and attack.
It really is that simple.
I'm telling you, just fight the way you always do.
Right!
All right!
I hear some go-go Karasuno cheers.
Let's go shut him up!
Yes, sir!
Maru!
Yeah!
Nice receive!
We didn't come here for a participation award.
We came here...
...to win!
They did it!
Tsubakihara was a brilliant show of unstoppable teamwork!
Yeah!
And this guy's gonna get straight to Toronomare!
Nice kill, boys!
All right, their number 10's in the back now!
It's true.
I do feel better with their number 10 in the back row.
But things have still taken a turn for the worse for me.
Because now the annoyingly relentless blocker who managed to stop Ushiwaka is right up front.
One touch!
Dainji!
Finish it!
One touch!
Chance ball!
Nice, Michael!
What a tremendous rally!
I tell you this, Joe!
Both of these teams seem to be feeling it now!
Tara!
Three!
Number four, Tara Damari.
He's got the heightened power of a professional.
But he tends to use cross shots over everything else.
Ready?
Ha!
Don't sell me short!
A line shot!
What?
Whoa!
Uh!
I was too far forward!
Nice save!
Azahi!
Yes!
Yeah!
Man!
I just can't tell if Hinata has a bunch of good luck or bad luck!
Neither!
Huh?
Hinata meant to be standing in that spot at that moment!
Uh!
Back Row Attack!
A dink?
Ah!
Too Far Forward Again?
Uh!
Get the Last Hit Over!
Come on Tanaka!
Uh!
Out!
You need more than determination to score, Tanaka.
Yes, sir.
It's only tryouts, and he's already being a dillweed.
Instincts are good, though.
That guy could end up on the team.
Wow.
He hit the ball to the perfect spot.
He's gotten so much better.
Echi-Joe, finish it.
And the setter, Kageyama makes first contact.
They prevent a variety of attacks by sending the ball straight at Karasuno's setter.
Tsukishima!
On it!
Over here!
Asahi!
Even when he's not the best at something, Tsukishima manages to pull it off.
Still, this shot is going to have a little awkwardness.
Along with a whole lot of intention.
Finish it!
That set was low and sloppy!
I'm almost emotional.
Three blockers!
Hooray!
Number three, Asamane smashes the ball off three Tsubakihara blockers,
giving the Karasuno crows their second point in a row.
Look at little Asahi.
He's really grown into his own, and not just his beautiful hair, either.
Yep, looks like it.
Tsukishima!
Nice set there.
Oh, thanks.
It really is hard to get a sense of the dimensions in here.
Frankly, that was mostly luck.
Hmm?
Could you maybe restrain yourself and not react exactly like Hinata?
What?
Man, does number ten enjoy getting hit in the face?
Use your hands, Tummy!
He wasn't just relying on his usual animal instincts.
He was reading the play.
Right.
Just because it's not a powerful hit,
doesn't mean they're going to dump it up front.
Nice deflection!
Jet ball!
Get him, Hinata!
Back minus tempo!
Oh!
Even from the back row, his attacks are incredibly fast!
Show your Hinata as something else, Cho!
Go, go, Kurosu no!
Don't panic!
Just take it one point at a time!
Yes, sir!
Damn it!
No worries.
We're getting to most shots.
Keep a close eye on their blockers.
Dude, that little number ten from Kurosu no looks like he's floating on air!
His receipts are awful, but he's a damn good attacker.
Um, Suga, what exactly is that?
Back minus?
It's Hinata and Kageyama's minus tempo attack, but done from the back row.
Sounds pretty cool, doesn't it?
How about adding thunder at the end?
No, then it would sound like one of your special moves, Nishi.
Hey.
Hey!
When this timeout is over, you better not blow your serve.
Duh, of course not!
Out!
I'm sorry!
Okay, my turn.
Hisushi!
You can do this, man!
Aim at four.
That's out!
No!
I'm sorry about that.
You'll get it next time.
I mean, I feel like I was a lot calmer than I thought I would be,
and I hit it in the direction I wanted it to go.
That was really good for me.
That's right.
Get hungry for more.
And there it is!
Karasuno High School is in position to take the first set.
Dammit.
Does he have to be the one serving now?
Tomaki High!
Do our guy!
Son of a bitch!
Shake it off!
Don't even sweat it!
Hmm.
Subaki Heart Academy has chosen to bring in a substitute.
First-year pinch server, Himakawa.
I believe that this will actually be his first official match there, Joe.
Let's see how he handles the pressure.
Yikes.
Huh?
He's even more nervous than I am.
Hmm.
You
Yeah, don't just sit there makes him know it's really lucky
He blew it
Oh, Mrs. And Underham, sir
Made him look like an ass
He'll have nightmares about that for the rest of his life
Seriously, man?
I'm so sorry
Yeah, I know
It was such a beautiful sound
If you gotta hit somebody out there, make sure it's not me
Hey, aren't you being a little harsh, dude?
It's bad, but our serves kind of sucked the whole second half
I know, I already said I'm sorry
Won't get anywhere if our serves don't land in the court
I'm aware of that
Right, you guys all warmed up?
Yes
I'm warmed up to the point of exhaustion
That's enough
You ever do that again and I'll kill you
I'm still having a hard time
I'm getting a feel for this place
Yeah, it's not that easy
Nice kill
Hey, Makawa
Start pretty bad for me and I will kick your ass, man
Coach will put me in the starting lineup for our next game
You just think about how to make the best use of the few chances you're gonna get
Of all the possible plays on the court
The one where it's hardest to control your mindset is the serve
When you mess up, it's not your teammates who refuse to forgive you
It's yourself
So he's trying again
A ceiling serve?
It's not fast enough that they can't react
And not powerful enough to blow any of them away
I got it
But it's still
Quite effective
Sorry
Right now
The ceiling
Is on my side
That guy's ceiling serve
Was so cool
Mine, got it
Uh oh
Karasuno just let the ball hit the floor
That's two services in a row for young Himakawa
Giving Tsubaki Hara Academy the lead
Yeah
Got it
You, look
Up front
Nice receive
Karasuno is feeling the heat, Joe
They're calling their second time out
When you hit the ball
Just make sure you get it in the air
I don't care if it's short
But get it high
Sorry
We did it
The tide is back in our favor
Their guys are starting to panic
Let's keep it up
Yeah
Do it again, bro
Right
I don't really understand this tide thing
But
I know we're finally getting it together
Oh yeah
This is
Here it comes
Number 10 is
Wait
More guys coming from the sides
And the back
This is
The national tournament
Himakawa
Get ready for the third set
We'll need you
Right
80%
Holy Hokkaido
A flawless ace
Yes
Yeah
Karasuno High School
Is slowly closing in, Joe
Don't worry about it, guys
Remember
Turo Tamari's on our team
Talking about me
And Echi Joe
Is always keeping his cool
I guess, sure
That samurai guy over there
May have a super strong serve
But the four of us
Should be able to stop it
That's the point in the speech
Where we all wish
You would just say
That you'll handle it
You know who has a third here
Asi
Get us one more
Got it
Oh, he dumps it like a Komatsu backhoe
This team is not ready to go home yet
Yeah
That Captain Echi Joe
Knows how to get results, my friend
It takes some real guts
To pull that move off
In such a critical moment
But hey
That's a third year for you
Really?
Already?
Damn it
I can tell he's blaming this on me
But that was definitely higher than usual
What he said
This team isn't ready
To go home yet
Match point
If they get this, they win
Come on
Kageyama said this was just another step towards the goal
But for me
It feels like I'm already here
Like this is the goal
Good job, man
Make us proud
Do it, Suga
I can't really tell if I'm still nervous or not
You got this, Suga
But my mind is clear
We're counting on you, Suga
I know what I have to do
Bring it on!
Oh, looks like their receive was a bit shaky
That's because he aimed for a spot where the setter would have to get the ball
Not wrong there, Joe
Number four
Tera Domari
He's got both height and power
Usually hits the ball in exactly the direction he's facing
Little help
Tanaka!
That was perfect
Oh, hell yeah!
Damn it
That was a weaker spike
Maru!
Three blockers!
Black, black!
Number one
Maruyama
That ball went flying off the blockers' hands!
Doesn't matter though
Koshi Sugawara's under it!
Maruyama's got solid fundamentals
He's great at wipes
But there's always a chance he'll go for a dink
I saw Karasuno play at nationals
That's why I chose this school
Thank you for having us
Even so
If we get another chance
Grab it
Let's go!
Take them down!
Oh, man, fortune favors the prepared mind.
Thank you.